{
    "quiz": {
        "question": [
            {
                "id": 214,
                "_id": "09-01",
                "chapterId": 9,
                "question": "The only way to accurately show a programâ€™s effect involves collecting _____ about target populations before the program begins.",
                "refPage": "222",
                "possible0": "operating data",
                "possible1": "impact statements",
                "possible2": "baseline information",
                "possible3": "implementation methods",
                "correctAnswer": 2,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 215,
                "_id": "09-02",
                "chapterId": 9,
                "question": "Being able to compare conditions before a program begins to after it has been operating for a set amount of time is the goal of:",
                "refPage": "222",
                "possible0": "formation",
                "possible1": "education",
                "possible2": "evaluation",
                "possible3": "modification",
                "correctAnswer": 2,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 216,
                "_id": "09-03",
                "chapterId": 9,
                "question": "A component of impact _____ includes measuring if learning has occurred within a target population.",
                "refPage": "222",
                "possible0": "overviews",
                "possible1": "evaluation",
                "possible2": "instruments",
                "possible3": "administration",
                "correctAnswer": 1,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 217,
                "_id": "09-04",
                "chapterId": 9,
                "question": "So that multiple evaluators can reliably administer them, the FLSE II must design _____ evaluation instruments.",
                "refPage": "222",
                "possible0": "multiple",
                "possible1": "universal",
                "possible2": "retractable",
                "possible3": "reproducible",
                "correctAnswer": 3,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 218,
                "_id": "09-05",
                "chapterId": 9,
                "question": "A good written test uses several _____ so that ascending levels of the cognitive process can be evaluated.",
                "refPage": "223",
                "possible0": "types of distractors",
                "possible1": "instructional formats",
                "possible2": "formats of questions",
                "possible3": "coordinated measurements",
                "correctAnswer": 2,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 219,
                "_id": "09-06",
                "chapterId": 9,
                "question": "The gold standard of measuring knowledge gain is through:",
                "refPage": "223",
                "possible0": "learning goals.",
                "possible1": "school-based delivery.",
                "possible2": "pretesting/posttesting.",
                "possible3": "response-limited evaluations.",
                "correctAnswer": 2,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 220,
                "_id": "09-07",
                "chapterId": 9,
                "question": "Pretests and posttests should be administered _____ a lesson or program has been delivered.",
                "refPage": "225",
                "possible0": "after",
                "possible1": "before",
                "possible2": "before and after",
                "possible3": "immediately before and immediately after",
                "correctAnswer": 2,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 221,
                "_id": "09-08",
                "chapterId": 9,
                "question": "What should be administered for school-based and community-based audiences before and after a lesson or program has been delivered?",
                "refPage": "225",
                "possible0": "Direct observations",
                "possible1": "Indirect inspections",
                "possible2": "Goals and objectives",
                "possible3": "Pretests and posttests",
                "correctAnswer": 3,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 222,
                "_id": "09-09",
                "chapterId": 9,
                "question": "The form of evaluation used by FLSE IIs to view the skill implementation of learners is referred to as:",
                "refPage": "225",
                "possible0": "pretest.",
                "possible1": "posttest.",
                "possible2": "direct observation.",
                "possible3": "indirect observation.",
                "correctAnswer": 2,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 223,
                "_id": "09-10",
                "chapterId": 9,
                "question": "An evaluator uses _____, which is a form of evaluation, when he or she wants to physically examine an environment in search of proof that behavioral change has occurred.",
                "refPage": "225",
                "possible0": "a pretest",
                "possible1": "a posttest",
                "possible2": "direct inspection",
                "possible3": "direct observation",
                "correctAnswer": 2,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 224,
                "_id": "09-11",
                "chapterId": 9,
                "question": "Which type of evaluation is designed to evaluate the opinions, attitudes, and values about a specific topic across a population of learners?",
                "refPage": "226",
                "possible0": "Statistical",
                "possible1": "Test bank",
                "possible2": "Written survey",
                "possible3": "State accreditation",
                "correctAnswer": 2,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 225,
                "_id": "09-12",
                "chapterId": 9,
                "question": "Outcome/effectiveness studies measure the effect a program has upon:",
                "refPage": "226",
                "possible0": "FLSE IIs.",
                "possible1": "its target population.",
                "possible2": "different learning levels.",
                "possible3": "individuals with learning disabilities.",
                "correctAnswer": 1,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 226,
                "_id": "09-13",
                "chapterId": 9,
                "question": "Collected through tests and surveys, ___ means little until evaluators compile it into a useful format.",
                "refPage": "227",
                "possible0": "raw data",
                "possible1": "dynamics",
                "possible2": "design instruction",
                "possible3": "knowledge analysis",
                "correctAnswer": 0,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 227,
                "_id": "09-14",
                "chapterId": 9,
                "question": "Turning raw data collected through tests and surveys into useful information requires:",
                "refPage": "227",
                "possible0": "impact evaluation software.",
                "possible1": "accurate data entry and analysis.",
                "possible2": "multiple personnel from multiple agencies.",
                "possible3": "permission from the authority having jurisdiction (AHJ).",
                "correctAnswer": 1,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 228,
                "_id": "09-15",
                "chapterId": 9,
                "question": "To ensure the process of data collection captures data accurately, _____ are presented before the team enters the data.",
                "refPage": "227",
                "possible0": "responses",
                "possible1": "interpretations",
                "possible2": "statistical methods",
                "possible3": "data entry guidelines",
                "correctAnswer": 3,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 229,
                "_id": "09-16",
                "chapterId": 9,
                "question": "What two types of calculations are used to interpret knowledge gain data?",
                "refPage": "228",
                "possible0": "Tendency and frequency",
                "possible1": "Highest and lowest scores",
                "possible2": "Median of scores and modes",
                "possible3": "Mean of scores and percentages",
                "correctAnswer": 3,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 230,
                "_id": "09-17",
                "chapterId": 9,
                "question": "To calculate the _____ of a set of scores, add all the scores of the test and divide by the number of scores.",
                "refPage": "228",
                "possible0": "mode",
                "possible1": "percentage",
                "possible2": "statistical mean",
                "possible3": "statistical median",
                "correctAnswer": 2,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 231,
                "_id": "09-18",
                "chapterId": 9,
                "question": "To calculate the _____ of participants who returned a survey, divide the number of participants who returned the survey by the total number of participants who received the survey and then multiply by 100.",
                "refPage": "228",
                "possible0": "mode",
                "possible1": "percentage",
                "possible2": "statistical mean",
                "possible3": "statistical median",
                "correctAnswer": 1,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 232,
                "_id": "09-19",
                "chapterId": 9,
                "question": "Developing conclusions about program impact is based on an objective:",
                "refPage": "229",
                "possible0": "benchmark.",
                "possible1": "remediation plan.",
                "possible2": "understanding of knowledge gain.",
                "possible3": "interpretation of evaluation results.",
                "correctAnswer": 3,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 233,
                "_id": "09-20",
                "chapterId": 9,
                "question": "Once an impact study has been completed, the FLSE II should _____ staff, decision-makers, and the community at large.",
                "refPage": "230",
                "possible0": "challenge the",
                "possible1": "report results to",
                "possible2": "consider including",
                "possible3": "interpret the data for",
                "correctAnswer": 1,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 234,
                "_id": "09-21",
                "chapterId": 9,
                "question": "The best local resources for helping the FLSE with evaluation instruments are:",
                "refPage": "230",
                "possible0": "journalists.",
                "possible1": "grant writers.",
                "possible2": "administrative staff.",
                "possible3": "other professional educators.",
                "correctAnswer": 3,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            }
        ]
    }
}
